<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Components on</title><link>toni-moreno.github.io/snmpcollector.org/docs/components/</link><description>Recent content in Components on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="toni-moreno.github.io/snmpcollector.org/docs/components/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Variable Catalog</title><link>toni-moreno.github.io/snmpcollector.org/docs/components/variable-catalog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 08:43:34 +0100</pubDate><guid>toni-moreno.github.io/snmpcollector.org/docs/components/variable-catalog/</guid><description>View Available Variables are shown as table. This will appear every time you navigate from menu.
Add/Edit Variables to the catalog Add: In the catalog list click on new button Edit: In the catalog list click the edit&amp;rsquo;s button The Create/Modify form will show up:
Edit variables Configuration Parameters These are the following parameters, that let you create an usable Variable</description></item><item><title>InfluxDB Servers</title><link>toni-moreno.github.io/snmpcollector.org/docs/components/influx-servers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 08:43:34 +0100</pubDate><guid>toni-moreno.github.io/snmpcollector.org/docs/components/influx-servers/</guid><description>View Configured Influx Servers are shown as table. This will appear every time you navigate from menu.
influx servers list Add/Edit InfluxDB output databases Add: In the InfluxDB Servers list click on new button Edit: Click on InfluxDB edit&amp;rsquo;s button The Create/Modify form will show up:
New button Configuration Parameters These are the following parameters, that let you create an HTTP based InfluxDB Connection</description></item><item><title>OID Conditions</title><link>toni-moreno.github.io/snmpcollector.org/docs/components/oid-conditions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 08:43:34 +0100</pubDate><guid>toni-moreno.github.io/snmpcollector.org/docs/components/oid-conditions/</guid><description>View Configured OID Conditions are shown as table. This will appear every time you navigate from menu.
Add/Edit OID Conditions Add: In the OID Conditions list click on new button Edit: Click on OID Condition edit&amp;rsquo;s button The Create/Modify form will show up:
Configuration Parameters These are the following parameters that allow you to create an OID Condition to be applied as Measurement Filter on Measurement definitions</description></item><item><title>SNMP Metrics</title><link>toni-moreno.github.io/snmpcollector.org/docs/components/snmp-metrics/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 08:43:34 +0100</pubDate><guid>toni-moreno.github.io/snmpcollector.org/docs/components/snmp-metrics/</guid><description>View Configured SNMP Metrics are shown as table. This will appear every time you navigate from menu.
SNMP Metric List Add/Edit SNMP Metrics Add: In the SNMP Metrics list click on new button Edit: Click on SNMP Metric edit&amp;rsquo;s button The Create/Modify form will show up:
Create/Modify SNMP Metrics Configuration Parameters Type of settings Config Parameter Description Core settings ID Text String that uniquely identify the metric recommended use the MIB Name, should be unique in the database FieldName Set the &amp;ldquo;field&amp;rdquo; name inside a Influx measurement, could be the same of id or not, should be unique inside the measurement where the metric will be sent.</description></item><item><title>Measurements</title><link>toni-moreno.github.io/snmpcollector.org/docs/components/measurements/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 08:43:34 +0100</pubDate><guid>toni-moreno.github.io/snmpcollector.org/docs/components/measurements/</guid><description>Measurements When data are gathered from SNMP devices we can group them together as we wish when snmp data are scalar objects but is mandatory group snmp tabular objects in the same measurement.
View Configured Measurements are shown as table. This will appear every time you navigate from menu.
SNMP Measurements List Add/Edit Measurements Add: In the Measurements list click on new button Edit: Click on Measurement edit&amp;rsquo;s button The Create/Modify form will show up:</description></item><item><title>Measurement Groups</title><link>toni-moreno.github.io/snmpcollector.org/docs/components/measurement-groups/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 08:43:34 +0100</pubDate><guid>toni-moreno.github.io/snmpcollector.org/docs/components/measurement-groups/</guid><description>View Configured Measurement Groups are shown as table. This will appear every time you navigate from menu.
Add/Edit InfluxDB output databases Add: In the InfluxDB Servers list click on new button Edit: Click on InfluxDB edit&amp;rsquo;s button The Create/Modify form will show up:
Configuration Parameters Type of settings Config Parameter Description MeasurementGroups settings ID Text String that uniquely identify the measurement group recommended use the Product/Device Name/model as, should be unique in the database Measurements A list of measurement id&amp;rsquo;s Extra settings Description A description text for the measurement group.</description></item><item><title>Measurement Filters</title><link>toni-moreno.github.io/snmpcollector.org/docs/components/measurement-filters/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 08:43:34 +0100</pubDate><guid>toni-moreno.github.io/snmpcollector.org/docs/components/measurement-filters/</guid><description>View Configured Measurement Filters are shown as table. This will appear every time you navigate from menu.
Add/Edit Measurement Filters Add: In the Measurement Filters list click on new button Edit: Click on Measurement Filter edit&amp;rsquo;s button The Create/Modify form will show up:
Configuration Parameters Type of settings Config Parameter Description Core settings ID Text String for each MeasurementID The measurement on which filter could be applied if selected in the device.</description></item><item><title>Custom filters</title><link>toni-moreno.github.io/snmpcollector.org/docs/components/custom-filters/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 08:43:34 +0100</pubDate><guid>toni-moreno.github.io/snmpcollector.org/docs/components/custom-filters/</guid><description>View Configured Custom Filters are shown as table. This will appear every time you navigate from menu.
Custom Filters Add/Edit Custom Filters Add: In the Custom Filters list click on new button Edit: Click on Custom Filter edit&amp;rsquo;s button A modal will shown up with some steps that the user must complete:
1. Select related SNMP Device: Note:: Only valid when creating a new Custom Filter</description></item><item><title>SNMP Devices</title><link>toni-moreno.github.io/snmpcollector.org/docs/components/snmp-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 08:43:34 +0100</pubDate><guid>toni-moreno.github.io/snmpcollector.org/docs/components/snmp-devices/</guid><description>SNMP Devices The core component: SNMP Devices. The user will define Devices to poll data from using SNMP protocol.
View Configured SNMP Devices are shown as table. This will appear every time you navigate from menu.
Add/Edit SNMP Devices Add: In the SNMP Devices list click on new button Edit: Click on SNMP Devices edit&amp;rsquo;s button The Create/Modify form will show up:
Configuration Parameters Type of settings Config Parameter Description Core settings ID Text String that uniquely identify the device , should be unique in the config db, it can be hostname, serial number or any other text id Active let device begin gathering process on agent boot process Device settings Host the network direction the agent will use to do snmp connection , could be IP or fqdn name Port the network port where the agent will use to do snmp connections Timeout sets de timeout for each SNMP query Retries sets the number of retries to attempt within Timeout Alternate System OID&amp;rsquo;s Set OID to get like MIB-2::System Info for non MIB-2 based devices Debug settings LogLevel enable use select verbosity of the device log SnmpDebug if this option is set all snmp low level protocol queries with detailed info on this device will be written on a file with name &amp;ldquo;snmpdebug_XXXXXX.</description></item></channel></rss>