<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on</title><link>/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Runtime</title><link>/docs/runtime/runtime/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/runtime/runtime/</guid><description>SNMPCollector has an embedded online device state and data measurement viewer, which help us to monitor how data has been gathered for each device. On the device list you will see if device is active or have been stoped by the administrator. You can also see if there is any connectivity problems System description Runtime Operations Operation Description SNMP State Enable or disable online the selected SNMP Device Force Gather Execute a Complete Gathering process, useful for testing on not active devices or force again SNMP Debug Enable or disable SNMP Debugging Log Level Change Log level online Force Flt Update Force filter update on the next poll Download Log File Download the log file related with device Force SNMP Reset (soft) only restarts snmp connection for current established measurements and with current indexed states an filter states.</description></item><item><title/><link>/docs/data-management/export/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/data-management/export/</guid><description>EXPORTING A FILE To export a file the option &amp;ldquo;Export data&amp;rdquo; in the menu will be used.
This option allows the user to select different files to export. The steps will be the following:
1. Select type: The user can select one type at the same time of the following options:
2. Select Items of type: The user can select one or more items of the selected type and click on the arrow to add them to the exported file.</description></item><item><title/><link>/docs/data-management/import/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/data-management/import/</guid><description>IMPORTING A FILE To import a file the option &amp;ldquo;Import&amp;rdquo; in the menu will be used.
This option allows the user to select a file ( in this case a JSON file) and select two options:
AutoRename -&amp;gt; It allows to change the name of the file, is useful if u want to copy a device, measurement, etc and rename it. Overwrite -&amp;gt; It allows to overwrite the current file in the SNMP collector with the same name as the imported file.</description></item><item><title/><link>/docs/public-templates/public-device-dashboard-templates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/public-templates/public-device-dashboard-templates/</guid><description>From this page you will be able to download a definition and a dashboard from some popular devices/products.
Import Instructions SnmpCollector Template 1.-Download the json file and Import it, after you will see a new device with id=&amp;ldquo;localhost&amp;rdquo; 2.- Change the ID , host , port to define your linux box device, and test connectivity with the snmp connection tool 3.- Change the imported InfluxDB server to any of your previously defined influx servers</description></item><item><title/><link>/docs/troubleshooting/troubleshooting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/troubleshooting/troubleshooting/</guid><description>Review Logs snmpcollector has a complete set of log files to review all what is happening while gathering snmp data from our infrastructure. All logs are located in the same directory LOG_DIR.
Default LOG_DIR is at /var/log/snmpcollector if snmpcollector has been installed with debian and redhat based packages. is at /opt/snmpcollector/log in docker and always can be set with -log option passed to the snmpcollector binary.
If installed with debian/redhat packages you can also tune this parameters in these files</description></item></channel></rss>